(Bernadette:)Almost there.
You're doing great.
(Howard:)Thanks for lifting my spirits.
Next time, try lifting the box.
(Raj:)Please hurry.
l don't need a treadmill!
(Howard:)The doctor says you need
to get exercise!
I get plenty of exercise!
(Howard:)Crushing my will
to live isn't exercise!
(Raj:)If she isn't gonna use it,
then why are we doing this?
(Howard:)She'll use it.
All I need is to rig it
(Howard:)with a fishing pole
and a HoneyBaked ham.
(Raj:)All right.
(Raj:)Now what?
(Bernadette:)-We set it up in Howie's old room.
-Do you know how to set it up?
(Howard:)Please, I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
I think I can handle...
Ma, look out!
I told you this thing would kill me!
I (THEME SONG PLAYING) I